MANYU LAKHOTIA

 $+1(337)322-4192 \diamond LakeMonYew@gmail.com \diamond majorziploc.onrender.com \\ www.linkedin.com/in/majorziploc/ \diamond github.com/MajorZiploc \diamond majorziploc.itch.io/$

Software Developer with 8+ years of work experience in developing web applications, stand alone applications, cicd, and databases; along with personal experience in art/design, scripting, web scraping, gamedev, data analytics, and data cleaning.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Frontend/Design react, redux, jquery, css, sass, html, material ui, bootstrap, winforms, cypress.io, krita, inkscape

Backend/Testing/Headless django, express, nodejs, asp.net mvc, google app suite, jest, pandas, webscraper.io, tampermonkey

Languages javascript, python, typescript, bash, sql, mongodb, php, redis, java, C#, F#, powershell, rbql, vimscript

DevOps docker, aws, kubernetes, gitlab ci, github actions, ansible, Octopus Deploy, Teamcity, vmware

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer - Full time - Mostly Remote - Team size: 4-10 Acadian Ambulance (Medical) Mar 2020 - Apr 2022 and Aug 2024 - Present Lafayette, LA

- Leadership: Led development of an ambulance scheduling system
- Testing: Introduced automated UI and API testing using Cypress.io
- Utilized: F#, C#, react, redux, wsl, mssql, docker, just, bash, microservices, aws, Octopus Deploy, Teamcity

Software Engineer - Full time - Remote - Team size: 4-8 Optimal Dynamics (Logistics) Feb 2024 - Aug 2024 New York, NY

- Mapping: consume data from many customers in many formats to a unified format for processing
- Discovery: Undertook greenfield development and research to scout new projects
- Utilized: react, redux, postgresql, django, celery, rabbitmq, docker, redis, spring boot, bash, microservices, aws

Software Engineer - Full time - Remote - Team size: 4-8 Conservis (Agriculture) May 2022 - Jan 2024 Minneapolis, MN

- Security: Improved authentication by moving from homebrewed auth solution to keycloak
- Design: Use krita and inkscape to design frontend mockups and create syg icons
- Utilized: react, redux, postgresql, django, celery, rabbitmq, docker, redis, spring boot, bash, microservices, aws

Software Developer - Part time - Remote - Team size: 3-5 Cythereal (Cyber security)

Jun 2021 - Apr 2022 Lafayette, LA

- Visualization: Created dashboard to investigate potential malware samples
- Utilized: django, react, redux, docker, mongodb, redis, rpm, bash, azure, ansible, terraform, packer, just

Software Developer - Full time - Hybrid - Team size: 10-15 CGI (Medical) Jan 2019 - Feb 2020 Lafayette, LA

- Modernization: Migrated legacy health insurance portal to more modern solutions
- Utilized: django, react, redux, docker, redis, mongodb, bash, openshift, vscode

Software Developer - Part time - Hybrid - Team size: 4-6 Wetlands Research Center (Aquaculture) Dec 2016 - Apr 2018 Lafayette, LA

tlands Research Center (Aquaculture)

OPEN SOURCE PROJECTS

 $\textbf{F\# projects with contributions} \ F S harp Plus, \ A cadian. F S harp, \ A cadian. D apper. Fs, \ A cadian. J s on. Fs \ (A vailable on nuget)$

Processing: Developed a stand alone java swing app for analyzing geospatial water levels from large NetCDF files

nvim-dev-container A nvim plugin for containers.dev support (Available on github) (lua)

keycloak A oauth2 library with user federations, management and more (Available on maven) (java)

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Economics with Computer Science and Mathematics, University of Louisiana at Lafayette 201

2016 - 2018

Associates in General Studies Business, South Louisiana Community College

2013 - 2015